Please kindly read this before using:

## Folder Structure:
+ documentation: includes on how to setup & use the theme; document for embeded 3rd party plugins: Slider Revolution, Visual Composer --> READ THIS FIRST please.
+ demo-content: includes demo data to make it same as our live demo including pages demo, slider...
+ licensing: licensing policy
+ exploore: the theme source code, the unzip version of the theme
+ exploore-child: child theme so you can customize via this child theme and it won;t giev any impact to the theme itself, you can easily update the theme later without touching the core theme files.
+ exploore.zip: the installation WordPress theme zip file.

